HARITHA THANKACHAN

Software Engineer

CONTACT

8547496485

★ harithak17@gmail.com

Q Cochin

EDUCATION

CUSAT

2009 - 2013

B.Tech in Information Technology

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML,CSS, Java Script,Bootstratp
- Core Java
- J2EE framework
- JSP Servlets
- · Spring Framework.
- · Spring MVC
- Springboot
- JPA, JDBC
- MySql,Oracle
- · Eclipse, IntelliJ IDEA
- Git
- · Data Structures and Algorithms
- RESTful Webservices

PROFILE

I am an experienced Software Engineer offering 5years of experience in demanding environments. Skilled in directing development with creative and performance-oriented approach. Well-organized and customer-focused with proven skills in project development and team activities. Completed B-tech in Information Technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BEO Softwares Pvt Ltd

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (Jan 2019- Sept 2021)

- Development and Support for the Live Enterprise Application ATLAS
- Ensuring test coverage and code quality using SonarQube.
- Develop codes based on user requirements documentation and detailed design documentation.
- Resolve system defects and perform bug fixes during testing phase.
- Perform unit testing of application codes.

DANTEK Technologies

JAVA DEVELOPER (Jan 2016 - Oct 2018)

- Worked on a software product based on based on ERP business process. It includes product management, supply chain (purchasing ,manufacturing ,distribution) financials, warehouse management, sales order processing, and Quality and Testing.
- Development and Implementation of various modules.
- · Generating graphical representation of data.
- Generating pdf, excel reports of data.

GTec Computer Educations

SOFTWARE PROGRAMMING TRAINER (May 2014- Dec 2015)

- · Guided academic projects for BCA students in VB6.
- Trained DCA,PGDCA students.
- Trained students in C,C++,Java,OOPS Concepts.
- Trained students in Computer basics, Programming basics and open office.